

VOCATIONAL DIPLOMA SUPPLEMENT NO. DZ/11009112/24 *



NAME(S) AND SURNAME OF THE DIPLOMA HOLDER BŁAŻEJ STANISŁAW FEDEROWICZ

1. TITLE OF THE DIPLOMA ¹⁾	10
Dyplom zawodowy w zawodzie Technik informatyk 351203	
¹⁾ Original language version.	

2. TRANSLATED TITLE OF THE DIPLOMA 2)

VOCATIONAL DIPLOMA Information technology technician 351203

2) If applicable. This translation has no legal status.

3. PROFILE OF SKILLS AND COMPETENCES

The vocational diploma for the occupation of an information technology technician certifies that the holder is able to:

- apply rules of cyber security and netiquette,
- assemble a computer from subassemblies,
- upgrade computers,
- configure and manage Windows and Linux operating systems,
- install and configure operating systems and application programs,
- secure operating systems from malware, uncontrolled flow of information and data loss,
- recover data from computer technology devices,
- operate peripheral devices,
- diagnose damage to computer technology devices,
- repair computer technology equipment,
- select components and subassemblies of a local computer network,
- create models and diagrams of local area networks,
- install local area network cabling,
- perform testing and analysis of local area networks,
- design local area networks,
- connect local area network to the Internet,
- operate local area networks,
- operate network equipment,
- administer server operating systems,
- use HyperText Markup Language (HTML) when designing web pages,
- use Content Management System (CMS),
- design computer graphics,
- make websites according to designs,
- publish websites and web applications,
- use Structured Query Language (SQL),
- design databases in a structured approach,
- create databases and modify their structure,
- administer databases,
- configure web applications,
- organise work and a workplace in accordance with the principles of occupational safety and hygiene, legal provisions on fire protection and environmental protection and the requirements of ergonomics,
- follow the rules of culture and professional ethics in communication with other people,
- organise and manage the work of a small team.

4. RANGE OF OCCUPATIONS ACCESSIBLE TO THE DIPLOMA HOLDER 3)

Information technology technician

3) If applicable.



SKILLS

- Effective teamwork capabilities
- Backend technologies:EJS, Node.js, Laravel
- Frontend Technologies: HTML, CSS, JS, ¡Query, React.js, Vue.js, BS, TW
- Version control (Git)

LANGUAGES

- English
- German
- Polish

HOBBIES

- Gym
- Traveling
- Playing guitar
- Web applications
- Animals

Contact



https://blazej-federowicz.vercel.app



Głodowo 67a, 83-412



+48 725 896 677



blazejfederowicz@gmail.com

Błażej Federowicz

SUMMARY

Motivated Information Technology Technician with fluent knowledge of **English** at the B2 CEFR and basic knowledge of German. I possess computer skills, including experience with key programs such as Excel, Word, and PowerPoint. I also have skills in web technologies, such as HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind and Git I am familiar with the basics of technologies like PHP, MySQL, Node.js, Vue.js, Laravel and **Python**. I confirm the application of my technical skills through my Portfolio: blazejfederowicz.vercel.app

EXPERIENCE

May 2022 - June 2022 Computer Technician Intern, Compus, Kościerzyna

- Diagnosing and replacing damaged or malfunctioning LCD/LED panels in monitors.
- Installing, configuring, and troubleshooting **printers,** including both wired and wireless models.
- Servicing, Repair, and Operational Management of Computer Hardware and Peripherals
- Documentation & Reporting.

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023 Game Dev Intern. Art of Code

- Developed physics interactions using Godot's built-in physics engine and GDScript, improving simulation accuracy by 22% and reducing performance issues by 30%.
- Crafting **Assets Design** from Scratch

Nationality Polish

Driver's license Yes

Date of birth 25.01.2004

July 2023 - August 2023 Industrial Worker, Savex Foods (Contract), Kościerzyna

 Following instructions and working with a team to package diffrent type of rice

EDUCATION

September 2019 - May 2024 Secondary School, PZS 2 in Kościerzyna

• IT Technician qualification with 90% in professional exams.

CERTIFICATIONS

August 2023 Responsive web design



https://www.freecodecamp .org/certification/Fabiio/res ponsive-web-design

October 2023 Legacy JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures



https://www.freecodecamp .org/certification/Fabiio/jav ascript-algorithms-anddata-structures